>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我在思考这个问题的时候
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A while back I was
thinking about this question of why people
说你为什么不能让他们自说自话
say well,
why couldn't you just make them autobound?
这样我就不用每次都做这个任务了吗
And make it so that I don't have
to do this assignment every time?
无法为我自动执行此操作吗 ?
Couldn't JavaScript just do
this automatically for me?
其实我觉得有一个方案。
In fact I think there is a proposal.
我不知道它是否会发生但我认为
I don't know if it's ever gonna happen,
but I think there is a proposal for
名为 @bound的类修饰符
a class decorator called @bound,
这将使您的所有类方法自动绑定。
which would make all your
class methods auto-bound.
所以这至少是他们在某种程度上正在考虑的事情
So this is at least something that
they're considering doing at some point,
使您能够选择此自动绑定。
is making it so
that you can opt into this auto-bound.
你也许能从我的语调里看出来
And you probably can tell from my tone,
在这一点上我不认为这是个好主意
at this point,
that I don't think that's a great idea.
但我想通过一个代码思考实验来说明为什么这个想法很糟糕。
But I wanna illustrate why it's such a bad
idea through a code thought experiment.
我坐下来想，我们怎么做呢 ?
I sat down and I thought,
how would we make it so
我们可以在原型上使用
that we could have methods on a prototype,
but
还会有自动硬绑定的方法来响应这些实例吗 ?
somehow also have auto hardbound
methods that respond to the instances?
我得出结论，这有一个黑客。
And I came to the conclusion,
there's a hack for this.
这就是它的样子
And here's what it looks like.
我们要做的是，我不希望你读这个代码。
What we will do is, and
I'm not expecting you to read this code.
如果你真的有兴趣的话我可以放大
I could zoom in if you were
really interested, but
我不希望你读这个代码
I'm not expecting you to read this code.
只是这个特殊的实用程序
It's just that this particular
utility method takes an existing
对一个原型对象进行方法，并将其替换为 getter方法。
method on one of your prototype objects,
and replaces it with a getter.
换句话说，不是用你的真实方法在你的类原型上，
So in other words, instead of having your
real method on your class prototype,
你会有一个消气的
you're gonna have a getter.
因此当您通过 getter 方法访问该属性名时，
So when you access that property
name through the getter,
自动创建硬绑定方法
it automatically creates
a hard bound method for
你会飞了然后把它保存到 WeakMap里
you on the fly, and
then saves it into a WeakMap.
它将它高速缓存到 WeakMap 和
So it caches it into a WeakMap and
然后通过吸气剂把它发给你
then sends it out to you
through by way of a getter.
换句话说， getter 方法就像代理程序自动发送这些硬
In other words, the getter is acting like
a proxy to automatically vend these hard
绑定或这些自动绑定功能。
bound or
these auto hard bound functions for you.
这样你就能得到一个在原型上拥有一个功能的好处
And so you get the benefit of having
a function on the prototype that can
继承。
be inherited.
但每次你把它当作一个背景点
But every time you access
it as a context dot,
你会得到一个硬版的
you're gonna get a hard
bound version of it.
这说明了为什么这是一个糟糕的想法。
This is an illustration of why
this is such a terrible idea.
要去那种程度的丑陋的奇事才能找到工作
To have to go to that kinda level of
ugly hackery to get something to work,
它只是不符合 JavaScript 函数的 DNA
it just doesn't fit with the DNA
of JavaScript's functions.
此感知函数的整个目的是使它们可以是动态的。
The whole purpose of this aware functions
is so that they can be dynamic.
试图强迫他们进入另一个工作模式
And trying to force them into
this other mode of working,
就像其他语言一样
which is like classes in other languages,
所以我们才会有这么大的烂烂
is why we wind up with
terrible hacky crap like that.
但是人们喜欢这样做
But, people like to do that and
这可能最终直接降落在 JavaScript中
this might actually end up landing
natively, directly in JavaScript.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你是这样用的，这个疯狂的小实用程序。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's how you use that
by the way, this crazy little utility.
只需调用该绑定方法即可使用它
You can use it by simply
calling that bind methods
任何类的原型的实用程序。
utility on the prototype of any class.
它会自动完成所有种类的原型
And it'll automatically go through
all of your class prototype methods,
并将其替换为自动绑定方法的 getter 版本。
and replace them with getter versions
that do the auto-bind method.
在我的恐惧中我在另一天发推特说
And to my horror, I tweeted this
out the other day to say hey,
这是个很糟糕的主意这就是原因
this is a really bad idea and here's why.
然后我接到一些人的回应说
And then I got several
responses from people saying
我现在正用这个来做我的项目
I'm now using this in my projects.
>> 扬声器 2: [LAUGH] >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 因此，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So,
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: One of the famous quotes,
我都不知道是谁给的，但我喜欢的名言就是
I don't even know who to attribute it to,
but famous quotes that I love is there's
没有比临时黑客更长久的了
nothing more permanent
than a temporary hacker.